Guide to the Rice University Alumni Affairs / University Events records, 1992-2012 UA 386
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Alumni Affairs / University Events records
1992-2012
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 386
2.75 Linear Feet
The records reflect the annual alumni events overseen by the Alumni Affairs office between the years of 1992 and 2012 and supervised by Jennifer Harding, Director of Reunion Programs and Special Events.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Alumni Affairs, in association with the Association of Rice Alumni, maintains communication with Rice alumni, encouraging them to stay connected with the University intellectually and socially and to assist in maintaining the welfare of the University.
Scope and Contents
The records reflect the annual alumni events overseen by the Alumni Affairs office between the years of 1992 and 2012 and supervised by Jennifer Harding, Director of Reunion Programs and Special Events.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to the public.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Received from Jennifer Harding, Director of Reunion Programs and Special Events, Aug. 12, 2005.
Related Materials
See also Office of Alumni Affairs Homecoming and Reunions Records, 1974-1991, UA 208, Woodson Research Center, Fondren Library, Rice University.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Universities and colleges
- 1992
  - American Music Festival, 1992-11-02-1992-11-08 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Homecoming, 1992-11-05-1992-11-08 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1932-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Association of Rice Alumni convocation and annual meeting, 1992-11-07 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1993
  - Homecoming, 1993-10-22-1993-10-24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1933-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1968-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1994
  - Homecoming, 1994-11-04-1994-11-05 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1929-1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1959-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1995
  - Homecoming, 1995-12-01-1995-12-02 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1930-1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1965-1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1996
  - Mini reunion class of 1938, 1996-03-15 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Homecoming, 1996-11-01-1996-11-02 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1921-1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1951-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Non-Homecoming (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 1997
  - Homecoming, 1997-11-07-1997-11-09 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1922-1942 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1952-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 1998
  - Homecoming, 1998-11-11-1998-11-14 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1923-1948 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1953-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Art Gallery exhibition: Nicole Eisenman "Behavior", 1998-11-05-1998-12-13 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 1999
  - Homecoming, 1999-11-12-1999-11-14 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1924-1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1954-1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 2000
  - Crawfish boil, 2000-04-08 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Praying Rice Owls, 2000-10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Rice Engineering Alumni awards, 2000-11-03 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Homecoming, 2000-11-03-2000-11-05 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1920-1960 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1965-1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 2001
  - "Measuring Alumni Affairs results", 2001-03-29 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Rice Engineering Alumni, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Homecoming, 2001-11-09-2001-11-11 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1926-1956 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1961-1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Rice Young Alumni, 2001-11-09-2001-11-11 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1955 Memorial Dedication Ceremony (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Rice University Chinese Alumni Association, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 2002
  - Crawfish Boil & Rice Baseball, 2002-04-20 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Cookout before the game-Rice vs. Houston, 2002-08-31 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Homecoming, 2002-11-15-2002-11-17 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1927-1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1972-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "Get Involved", 2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- 2003
  - Crawfish Boil & Rice Baseball, 2003-04-19 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Pregame events, 8-30, 9-20, 11-8-2003 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Homecoming, 2003-11-07-2003-11-09 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
  - Homecoming class reunions (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1963-1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- 2004
  - Homecoming, 2004-11-05-2004-11-07 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Homecoming class reuniuons, 1924-1954 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1959-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 2005
  - Summer luncheons, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hurricane Katrina, 2005-09 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fall Gathering class of 1939, 2005-09-27 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Homecoming, 2005-11-11-2005-11-13 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1960-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 2006
  - Homecoming, 2006-11-17-2006-11-19 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1926-1956 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1961-2006 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Non-Homecoming, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- 2007
  - Homecoming, 2007-11-02-2007-11-04 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
- 2008
  - Art Gallery: Michael A. Salter "Too Much", 2008-11-06-2008-12-14 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Centennial Campaign Lecture Series, 2008-11-07-2008-11-08 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Homecoming, 2008-11-07-2008-11-09 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1943-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1973-2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Society of Latino Alumni of Rice, 12-6, 1-29-09, 3-09 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- 2009
  - Homecoming, 2009-11-13-2009-11-15 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Homecoming class reunion notices, 2009-11-13-2009-11-15 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 2011
  - Homecoming, 2011-11-04-2011-11-06 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Homecoming class reunions, 1951, 1956, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Centennial announcement, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- 2012
  - Alumni College, 2012-03-09-2012-03-11 (Box 6, Folder 3)